Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
- Scripts
  - Rock, Roll and Remember
    - Show #04-33/1175, Aug 14-15, 2004; Summer Beach Party specialalso has handwritten date of Aug 13-14, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-34/1176, Aug 21-22, 2004; Al Greenalso has handwritten date of Aug 20-21, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-35/1177, Aug 28-29, 2004; Three Dog Night (Box 93)
    - Show #04-36/1178, Sep 4-5, 2004; Seals & Crofts (Box 93)
    - Show #04-37/1179, Sep 11-12, 2004; Cat Stevens (Box 94)
    - Show #04-38/1180, Sep 18-19, 2004; Sam Cooke (Box 94)
    - Show #04-39/1181, Sep 25-26, 2004; Jay & the Americans (Box 94)
    - Show #04-40/1182, Oct 2-3, 2004; Number Twos of Rock and Roll (Box 94)
    - Show #04-41/1183, Oct 9-10, 2004; Santana (Box 94)
    - Show #04-42/1184, Oct 16-17, 2004; Chicago (Box 94)
    - Show #04-43/1185, Oct 23-24, 2004; Paul McCartney; also has handwritten date of Oct 22-23, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-44/1186, Oct 30-31, 2004; Elvis Presley; also has handwritten date of Oct 29-30, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-45/1187, Nov 6-7, 2004; Number 1 hits; also has handwritten date of Nov 5-6, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-46/1188, Nov 13-14, 2004; Gary Puckett and the Union Gap; also has handwritten date of Nov 12-13, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-47/1189, Nov 20-21, 2004; Supremes; also has handwritten date of Nov 19-20, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-48/1190, Nov 27-28, 2004; Chuck Berry; also has handwritten date of Nov 26-27, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-49/1191, Dec 4-5, 2004; Dave Clark Five; also has handwritten date of Dec 3-4, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-50/1192, Dec 11-12, 2004; John Lennon; also has handwritten date of Dec 10-11, 2005 (Box 94)
    - Show #04-51/1193, Dec 18-19, 2004; Holiday special (Box 94)
    - Show #04-52/1194, Dec 25-26, 2004; Neil Diamond; also has handwritten date of Dec 17-18, 2005 (Box 95)
    - Show #05-01/1195, Jan 1-2, 2005; Number One Hits of Rock Era; also has handwritten date of Dec 31, 2005-Jan 1, 2006 (Box 95)
    - Show #05-02 through 05-52, 2005; cue sheets only; 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Show #06-01 through 06-53, 2006; cue sheets only; 4 folders (Box 95)
    - Show #07-01 through 07-28, 2007 Jan-Oct; cue sheets only; 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Show #07-29 through 07-52, 2007 Oct-Dec; cue sheets only; 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Show #08-01 through 08-52, 2008; cue sheets only; 5 folders (Box 96)
    - Show #09-01 through 09-52, 2009; cue sheets only; 3 folders (Box 96)
  - Sixties Party, undated (Box 97)
  - Summer Memories, 1990 Sep; Labor Day special (Box 97)
  - Summer Memories, 1991 Sep; Labor Day special (Box 97)
  - Summer Memories, undated; Labor Day special (Box 97)
  - U.S. Music Survey
    - Show #95-52, Dec 30-31, 1995; Best of 1995, Part 1 (Box 97)
    - Show #96-52, Dec 28-29, 1996; Best of 1996, Part 1 (Box 97)
    - Show #97-01, Jan 4-5, 1997; Best of 1996, Part 2 (Box 97)
    - Show #97-52, Dec 27-28, 1997; Best of 1997, Part 1 (Box 97)
    - Show #98-01, Jan 3-4, 1998; Best of 1997, Part 2 (Box 97)
    - Show #98-52, Dec 26-27, 1998; Best of 1998, Part 1 (Box 97)
    - Show #99-01, Jan 2-3, 1999; Best of 1998, Part 2 (Box 97)
    - Show #99-52, Dec 25-26, 1999; Best of 1999, Part 1 (Box 97)
    - Show #00-01, Jan 1-2, 2000; Best of 1999, Part 2 (Box 97)
    - Show #02-01, Jan 5-6, 2002 (Box 97)
    - Show #02-50, Dec 14-15, 2002 (Box 97)
    - Show #02-51, Dec 21-22, 2002 (Box 97)
    - Show #02-52, Dec 28-29, 2002 (Box 97)
    - Show #03-01, Jan 4-5, 2002 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-05, Feb 1-2, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-06, Feb 8-9, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-07, Feb 15-16, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-08, Feb 22-23, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-09, Mar 1-2, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-10, Mar 8-9, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-11, Mar 15-16, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-12, Mar 22-23, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-13, Mar 29-30, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-14, Apr 5-6, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-15, Apr 12-13, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-16, Apr 19-20, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-17, Apr 26-27, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-18, May 3-4, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-19, May 10-11, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-20, May 17-18, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-21, May 24-25, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-22, May 31-Jun 1, 2003 (Box 98)
    - Show #03-23, Jun 7-8, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-24, Jun 14-15, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-25, Jun 21-22, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-26, Jun 28-29, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-27, Jul 5-6, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-28, Jul 12-13, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-29, Jul 19-20, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-30, Jul 26-27, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-31, Aug 2-3, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-32, Aug 9-10, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-33, Aug 16-17, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-34, Aug 23-24, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-35, Aug 30-31, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-36, Sep 6-7, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-37, Sep 13-14, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-38, Sep 20-21, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-39, Sep 27-28, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-40, Oct 4-5, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-41, Oct 11-12, 2003 (Box 99)
    - Show #03-42, Oct 18-19, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-43, Oct 25-26, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-44, Nov 1-2, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-45, Nov 8-9, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-46, Nov 15-16, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-47, Nov 22-23, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-48, Nov 29-30, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-49, Dec 6-7, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-50, Dec 13-14, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-51, Dec 20-21, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #03-52, Dec 27-28, 2003 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-01, Jan 3-4, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-02, Jan 10-11, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-03, Jan 17-18, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-04, Jan 24-25, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-05 [not in collection], Feb 1-2, 2004
    - Show #04-06, Feb 7-8, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-07, Feb 14-15, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-08, Feb 21-22, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-09, Feb 28-29, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-10, Mar 6-7, 2004 (Box 100)
    - Show #04-11, Mar 13-14, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-12, Mar 20-21, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-13, Mar 27-28, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-14, Apr 3-4, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-15, Apr 10-11, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-16, Apr 17-18, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-17, Apr 24-25, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-18, May 1-2, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-19, May 8-9, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-20, May 15-16, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-21, May 22-23, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-22, May 29-30, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-23, Jun 5-6, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-24, Jun 12-013, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-25, Jun 19-20, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-26, Jun 26-27, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-27, Jul 3-4, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-28, Jul 10-11, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-29, Jul 17-18, 2004 (Box 101)
    - Show #04-30, Jul 24-25, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-31, Jul 31-Aug 1, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-32, Aug 7-8, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-33, Aug 14-15, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-34, Aug 21-22, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-35, Aug 28-29, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-36, Sep 4-5, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-37, Sep 11-12, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-38, Sep 18-19, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-39, Sep 25-26, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-40, Oct 2-3, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-41, Oct 9-10, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-42, Oct 16-17, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-43, Oct 23-24, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-44, Oct 30-31, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-45, Nov 6-7, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-46, Nov 13-14, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-47, Nov 20-21, 2004 (Box 102)
    - Show #04-48, Nov 27-28, 2004 (Box 103)
    - Show #04-49, Dec 4-5, 2004 (Box 103)
    - Show #04-50, Dec 11-12, 2004 (Box 103)
    - Show #04-51, Dec 18-19, 2004 (Box 103)
    - Show #04-52, Dec 25-26, 2004 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-01, Jan 1-2, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-02, Jan 8-9, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-03, Jan 15-16, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-04, Jan 22-23, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-05, Jan 29-30, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-06, Feb 5-6, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-07, Feb 12-13, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-08, Feb 19-20, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-09, Feb 26-27, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-10, Mar 5-6, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-11, Mar 12-13, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-12, Mar 19-20, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-13, Mar 26-27, 2005 (Box 103)
    - Show #05-14, Apr 2-3, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-15, Apr 9-10, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-16, Apr 16-17, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-17, Apr 23-24, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-18, Apr 30-May 1, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-19, May 7-8, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-20, May 14-15, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-21, May 21-22, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-22, May 28-29, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-23, Jun 4-5, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-24, Jun 11-12, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-25, Jun 18-19, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-26, Jun 25-26, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-27, Jul 2-3, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-28, Jul 9-10, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-29, Jul 16-17, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-30, Jul 23-24, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-31, Jul 30-31, 2005 (Box 104)
    - Show #05-32, Aug 6-7, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-33, Aug 13-14, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-34, Aug 20-21, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-35, Aug 27-28, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-36, Sep 3-4, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-37, Sep 10-11, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-38, Sep 17-18, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-39, Sep 24-25, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-40, Oct 1-2, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-41, Oct 8-9, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-42, Oct 15-16, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-43, Oct 22-23, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-44, Oct 29-30, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-45, Nov 5-6, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-46, Nov 12-13, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-47, Nov 19-20, 2005 (Box 105)
    - Show #05-48, Nov 26-27, 2005 (Box 106)
    - Show #05-49, Dec 3-4, 2005 (Box 106)
    - Show #05-50, Dec 10-11, 2005 (Box 106)
    - Show #05-51, Dec 17-18, 2005 (Box 106)
    - Show #05-52, Dec 24-25, 2005 (Box 106)
    - Show #05-48 and 05-51 ALT (Box 106)
    - Show #05-49 and 05-52 ALT (Box 106)
  - Where the Action Is, S05/E02, 2 Sep, 1965; television show episode (Box 106)
- TV Guides
  - Bound volumes
    - TV Guide, May 1955-Dec 1958 (Box 107)
    - TV Guide, 1959-1961 (Box 108)
    - TV Guide, 1962; Jan-Sep 1963;; Apr-Dec 1964;; Jan-Jun 1965 (Box 109)
    - TV Guide, Jul-Dec 1965; 1966-1967;; Jan-Jun 1968 (Box 110)
    - TV Guide, Jul-Dec 1968; 1969-1970;; Jan-Jun 1971 (Box 111)
    - TV Guide, Jul-Dec 1971; 1972-1973;; Jan-Mar 1974 (Box 112)
    - TV Guide, Apr-Dec 1974; 1975;; Jan-Mar 1976 (Box 113)
    - TV Guide, Apr-Dec 1976; 1977;; Jan-Mar 1978 (Box 114)
    - TV Guide, Apr-Dec 1978; 1979;; Jan-Mar 1980 (Box 115)
    - TV Guide, Apr-Dec 1980; 1981;; Jan-Mar 1982 (Box 116)
    - TV Guide, Apr-Dec 1982; 1983 (Box 117)
    - TV Guide, 1984; Jan-May 1985 (Box 118)
    - TV Guide, May-Dec 1985; Jan-Sep 1986 (Box 119)
    - TV Guide, Sep-Dec 1986; 1987 (Box 120)
    - TV Guide, 1988 [set 1]; Jan-Apr 1988 [set 2]; second 1988 set has a few gaps (Box 121)
    - TV Guide, May-Dec 1988 [set 2]; Jan-Nov 1989; second 1988 set has a few gaps (Box 122)
    - TV Guide, Dec 1989; 1990 (Box 123)
  - Unbound copies
    Each issue covered one week. Dates given below reflect this; for example, "July 2/8" refers to the week of July 2-8.
    - TV Guide, 1977: July 2/8 (Box 125)
    - TV Guide, 1984: Apr 28/May 4-Oct 13/19 (Box 125)
    - TV Guide, 1984: Oct 20/26-Nov 17/23, Dec 1/7-Dec 22/28 (Box 126)
    - TV Guide, 1985: Jan 5/11-Feb 16/22, Mar 2/8-16/22, Mar 30/Apr 5-Apr 6/12, Apr 20/26 (Box 126)
    - TV Guide, 1985: May 4/10-Jun 8/14, Jun 22/28-Jul 6/12, Jul 27/Aug 2-Nov 2/8 (Box 127)
    - TV Guide, 1985: Nov 9/15-16/22, Nov 30/Dec 6-Dec 27/Jan 3 (Box 128)
    - TV Guide, 1986: Jan 4/10-Apr 26/May 2 (Box 128)
    - TV Guide, 1986: May 3/9-Jul 26/Aug 1, Aug 9/15-Oct 11/17 (Box 129)
    - TV Guide, 1986: Oct 18/24-Dec 27/Jan 2 (Box 130)
    - TV Guide, 1987: Jan 3/9-Feb 28/Mar 6 (Box 130)
    - TV Guide, 1987: Mar 7/13-Jun 13/19 (Box 131)
    - TV Guide, 1987: Jun 20/26-Oct 10/16 (Box 132)
    - TV Guide, 1987: Oct 17/23-Dec 26/ Jan 1 (Box 133)
    - TV Guide, 1988: Jan 2/8-Jan 16/22 (Box 133)
    - TV Guide, 1988: Jan 23/Feb 2-Apr 16/22 (Box 134)
    - TV Guide, 1988: Apr 23/29-Sep 3/9 (Box 135)
    - TV Guide, 1988: Sep 10/16-Sep 17/23, Oct 8/14-Dec 31/Jan 6 (Box 136)
    - TV Guide, 1989: Jan 7/13-Jan 14/20, Feb 4/10-Mar 11/17 (Box 136)
    - TV Guide, 1989: Mar 18/24-Aug 26/Sep 1 (Box 137)
    - TV Guide, 1989: Sep 2/8-Dec 30/Jan 5 (Box 138)
    - TV Guide, 1990: Jan 6/12-Jan 20/26 (Box 138)
    - TV Guide, 1990: Feb 3/9-Feb 10/16, Mar 17/23-Apr 21/27, May 5/11-Sep 15/21 (Box 139)
    - TV Guide, 1990: Sep 22/28-Dec 29/Jan 4 (Box 140)
    - TV Guide, 1991: Jan 5/11-Jan 19/25 (Box 140)
    - TV Guide, 1991: Jan 26/Feb 1-May 4/10 (Box 141)
    - TV Guide, 1991: May 11/17-Aug 17/23 (Box 142)
    - TV Guide, 1991: Aug 24/30-Nov 23/29 (Box 143)
    - TV Guide, 1991: Nov 30/Dec 6-Dec 28/Jan 3 (Box 144)
    - TV Guide, 1992: Jan 4/10-Jan 11/17, Feb 1/7-Apr 4/10 (Box 144)
    - TV Guide, 1992: Apr 11/17-Jul 11/17 (Box 145)
    - TV Guide, 1992: Jul 18/24-Oct 10/16 (Box 146)
    - TV Guide, 1992: Oct 17/23-Dec 26/Jan 1 (Box 147)
    - TV Guide, 1993: Jan 2/8, 1993 (Box 147)
    - TV Guide, 1993: Jan 9/15-Mar 27/Apr 2 (Box 148)
    - TV Guide, 1993: Apr 3/9-Jun 19/25 (Box 149)
    - TV Guide, 1993: Jun 26/Jul 2-Sep 4/10 (Box 150)
    - TV Guide, 1993: Sep 11/17, Sep 25/Oct 1-Nov 20/26 (Box 151)
    - TV Guide, 1993: Nov 27/Dec 3-Dec 25/31 (Box 152)
    - TV Guide, 1994: Jan 1/7-Mar 12/18 (Box 152)
    - TV Guide, 1994: Mar 19/25-Sep 10/16 (Box 153)
    - TV Guide, 1994: Sep 17/23-Dec 31/Jan 6 (Box 154)
    - TV Guide, 1995: Jan 7/13-Feb 18/24 (Box 154)
    - TV Guide, 1995: Feb 25/Mar 3-Aug 12/18 (Box 155)
    - TV Guide, 1995: Aug 19/25-Dec 30/Jan 6 (Box 156)
    - TV Guide, 1996: Jan 7/13-Feb 3/9 (Box 156)
    - TV Guide, 1996: Feb 10/16-Aug 17/23 (Box 157)
    - TV Guide, 1996: Aug 24/30-Dec 28/Jan 3 (Box 158)
    - TV Guide, 1997: Jan 4/10-Feb 8/14 (Box 158)
    - TV Guide, 1997: Feb 15/21-Aug 2/8 (Box 159)
    - TV Guide, 1997: Aug 9/15-Dec 27/Jan 2 (Box 160)
    - TV Guide, 1998: Jan 3/9-Jan 24/30 (Box 160)
    - TV Guide, 1998: Jan 31/Feb 6-Jul 11/17 (Box 161)
    - TV Guide, 1998: Jul 18/24-Dec 26/Jan 1 (Box 162)
    - TV Guide, 1999: Jan 2/8-Jun 19/25 (Box 163)
    - TV Guide, 1999: Jun 26/Jul 2 (Box 164)
    - TV Guide, 2001: Feb 10/16 (Box 164)
    - TV Guide, 2002: Dec 28/Jan 3 (Box 164)
    - TV Guide, 2003: Jan 4/10-May 10/16 (Box 164)
    - TV Guide, 2003: May 17/23-May 24/30, Jun 7/13-Oct 4/10 (Box 165)
    - TV Guide, 2003: Oct 11/17-Nov 15/21 (Box 166)
- Miscellaneous
  - Artists profiled, RRR shows 1-199 (Box 106)
  - Cue sheets, blank (Box 106)
  - Dick Clark's Days to Remember, 3-9 Apr 2000; list of tracks and ad spots (Box 106)
  - Dick Clark's Days to Remember [copy 1], 4/3/00-4/9/00; clark_dtr_001; CD (Box 106)
  - Dick Clark's Days to Remember [copy 2], 4/3/00-4/9/00; clark_dtr_002; CD (Box 106)
  - Desk calendar, 2005; some pages annotated (Box 106)
  - Interviews by Laura Legs, list of groups and individuals, with 2-digit numbers ranging from 74 to 84; unclear if these are show numbers or dates (Box 106)
  - Interviews, RRR shows 154-194 (Box 106)
  - Man on street indices, list of names with brief notes on their responses, e.g. "Blake Maxon - Phoenix, AZ - MASH (it was funny), Paul Newman (likes movies he was in)" (Box 106)
  - Memorabilia, miscellaneous, includes 2 slides, program from 23rd AMA Special (Box 106)
  - Music Calendar, Jan 2005; list of dates and topics (Box 106)
  - Music Calendar, 2007-2009; lists of dates, topics, ad spots; 3 folders (Box 106)
  - Rock, Roll, and Remember Sweeps shows, lists of topics and music excerpts; 6 folders (Box 124)